Don Walker Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 28-131)
  - Show Music (Box 28-91, 107-126)
    - Glad to see you, 1944, Music by Jule Styne, lyrics by Sammy Cahn
      - I'm laying away a buck, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 61/1)
    - Go fight city hall, circa 1948-56, Alternate titles: 23 skidoo; Step into my parlor; Wicked, wicked city; Music and lyrics by Don Walker and Jack Lawrence
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - After saloon (Box-folder 61/2)
        - The age of chivalry (Box-folder 61/3)
        - The age of chivalry reprise (Box-folder 61/4)
        - Boarded up boarding house blues (Box-folder 61/5)
        - The collation cotillion (Box-folder 61/6)
        - Finale Act I: step into my parlor (Box-folder 61/7)
        - Finale Act I: the tenderloin (Box-folder 61/8)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 61/9)
        - How do you hold a sunbeam (Box-folder 61/10)
        - Howe and Hummel scene (Box-folder 61/11)
        - I hate the law (Box-folder 61/12)
        - Inside the little me, Reduced negative (Box-folder 61/13)
        - Introduction to Act I (Box-folder 61/14)
        - It's so peaceful Sunday morning (Box-folder 61/15)
        - It's so peaceful Sunday morning reprise and tag (Box-folder 61/16)
        - Just an age ago (Box-folder 61/17)
        - Just an age ago reprise (Box-folder 61/18)
        - Midsummer love (Box-folder 61/19)
        - O'Hara's oom-pah-pah (Box-folder 61/20)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 61/21)
        - There's a meetin' house around the corner (Box-folder 61/22)
        - Trial by petty jury (Box-folder 61/23)
        - Twenty-three skidoo (Box-folder 62/1)
        - Two man committee (Box-folder 62/2)
        - Who says crime doesn't pay (Box-folder 62/3)
        - The wicked, wicked city, Reverse transparency (Box-folder 62/4)
        - Lyric sheets (Box-folder 62/5)
        - Original lyrics (Box-folder 62/6)
      - Scripts
        - Script by Ira Wallach and Jack Lawrence (Box-folder 62/7)
        - Step into my parlor script by Ira Wallach and Jack Lawrence (Box-folder 62/8)
        - 23 skidoo original script (Box-folder 62/9)
        - 23 skidoo script (Box-folder 62/10)
        - 23 skidoo synopsis (Box-folder 62/11)
        - The wicked, wicked city synopsis (Box-folder 62/12)
        - Miscellaneous script material (Box-folder 62/13)
    - The happiest days, 1947, Music and lyrics by Charles Bick and Joe Sherman, book by Abby Mann and Bernard Drew
      - Script (Box-folder 62/14)
    - Hans Christian Andersen, circa 1975, London, Music and lyrics by Frank Loesser
      - Full scores
        - Ah, to be home again (Box-folder 117/1)
        - Anywhere I wander (Box-folder 117/2)
        - Anywhere I wander reprise (Box-folder 117/3)
        - Asking for trouble (Box-folder 117/4)
        - Ballet rehearsal (Box-folder 117/5)
        - Barabanchik (Box-folder 117/6)
        - Barabanchik exit (Box-folder 117/7)
        - Bows (Box-folder 117/8)
        - The classroom (Box-folder 117/9)
        - Don't introduce me to that angel (Box-folder 117/10)
        - Doro (Box-folder 117/11)
        - Ensemble trouble (Box-folder 117/12)
        - Entr'acte (Box-folder 117/13)
        - Fairy tale pantomime (parts I-IV) (Box-folder 117/14)
        - Farewell Otto (Box-folder 117/15)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 117/16)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 118/1)
        - Green room (Box-folder 118/2)
        - Happy new year (Box-folder 118/3)
        - He must go! (Box-folder 118/4)
        - The ice maiden (Box-folder 118/5)
        - I'm Hans Christian Andersen (Box-folder 118/6)
        - I'm Hans Christian Andersen exit (Box-folder 118/7)
        - I'm Hans Christian Andersen reprise (Box-folder 118/8)
        - In your eyes (Box-folder 118/9)
        - Inchworm (Box-folder 118/10)
        - Introduction to Act II (Box-folder 118/11)
        - Irate parents (Box-folder 118/12)
        - The king's new clothes (Box-folder 118/13)
        - The kiss (Box-folder 118/14)
        - The little mermaid (Box-folder 118/15)
        - No two people (Box-folder 119/1)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 119/2)
        - Otto (Box-folder 119/3)
        - Overture (Box-folder 119/4)
        - The poem (Box-folder 119/5)
        - Princess ballet (Box-folder 119/6)
        - Saunter away (Box-folder 119/7)
        - Second fantasy (Box-folder 119/8)
        - Siboni (Box-folder 119/9)
        - Something always happens (Box-folder 119/10)
        - Theater royal (Box-folder 119/11)
        - Thumbelina (Box-folder 119/12)
        - Tick-tock (Box-folder 119/13)
        - Truly loved (Box-folder 119/14)
        - A tune for humming (Box-folder 119/15)
        - The ugly duckling (Box-folder 119/16)
        - Wonderful Copenhagen (Box-folder 119/17)
        - Writing room (Box-folder 119/18)
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Ah, to be home again (Box-folder 63/1)
        - Anywhere I wander (Box-folder 63/2)
        - Asking for trouble (Box-folder 63/3)
        - Barabanchik (Box-folder 63/4)
        - Barabanchik exit (Box-folder 63/5)
        - Bows part I (Box-folder 63/6)
        - Bows part III (Box-folder 63/7)
        - The classroom (Box-folder 63/8)
        - Don't introduce me to that angel (Box-folder 63/9)
        - Doro (Box-folder 63/10)
        - Ensemble trouble (Box-folder 63/11)
        - Entr'acte (Box-folder 63/12)
        - Fairy tale pantomime (parts I-IV) (Box-folder 63/13-16)
        - Farewell Otto (Box-folder 63/17)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 63/18)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 63/19)
        - Green room (Box-folder 63/20)
        - Happy new year (Box-folder 63/21)
        - He must go (Box-folder 63/22)
        - The ice maiden (Box-folder 64/1)
        - I'm Hans Christian Andersen (Box-folder 64/2)
        - I'm Hans Christian Andersen reprise (Box-folder 64/3)
        - In your eyes (Box-folder 64/4)
        - Inchworm (Box-folder 64/5)
        - Irate parents (Box-folder 64/6)
        - The king's new clothes (Box-folder 64/7)
        - No two people (Box-folder 64/8)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 64/9)
        - Otto (Box-folder 64/10)
        - Overture (Box-folder 64/11)
        - The poem (Box-folder 64/12)
        - Royal Danish (Box-folder 64/13)
        - Saunter away (Box-folder 64/14)
        - Siboni (Box-folder 64/15)
        - Something always happens (Box-folder 64/16)
        - Theater Royal (Box-folder 64/17)
        - Thumbelina (Box-folder 64/18)
        - Truly loved (Box-folder 64/19)
        - A tune for humming (Box-folder 64/20)
        - The ugly duckling (Box-folder 64/21)
        - Wonderful Copenhagen (Box-folder 64/22)
        - Writing room (Box-folder 64/23)
        - Piano-vocal score, Photocopies (Box-folder 65/1)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 65/2)
      - Scripts
        - Hans Christian Andersen first draft script by Beverly Cross and Tommy Steele, 1974 May (Box-folder 65/3)
        - Hans Christian Andersen: A fairy of a tale of a life, various drafts of scripts by Don Walker (Box-folder 65/4-66/4)
        - Hans Andersen, London playing script by Beverly Cross and Tommy Steele (Box-folder 66/5)
        - Provisional rehearsal script, 1974 Oct. (Box-folder 66/6)
        - Rehearsal script, 1974 Nov. (Box-folder 66/7)
        - Research and scratch scenes (Box-folder 66/8)
      - Parts
        - Flutes I and II (Box-folder 67/1)
        - Oboe/English horn (Box-folder 67/2)
        - Clarinet I and II (Box-folder 67/3)
        - Bassoon (Box-folder 67/4)
        - Horn (Box-folder 67/5)
        - Trumpet I and II (Box-folder 67/6)
        - Trombone (Box-folder 67/7)
        - Percussion (Box-folder 67/8)
        - Violin I and II (Box-folder 67/9-10)
        - Viola (Box-folder 67/11)
        - Cello (Box-folder 67/12)
        - Bass (Box-folder 67/13)
        - Percussion, electronics and synthesizer, Bound (Box-folder 67/1)
        - Asking for trouble (Box-folder 68/1-2)
        - The classroom (Box-folder 68/3)
        - Fairy tale pantomime (parts I-IV) (Box-folder 68/4-7)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 69/1)
        - The ice maiden (Box-folder 69/2-3)
        - I'm Hans Christian Andersen (Box-folder 69/4)
        - I'm Hans Christian Andersen reprise (Box-folder 69/5)
        - Inchworm (Box-folder 69/6)
        - Thumbelina (Box-folder 69/7)
        - Tick-tock (Box-folder 69/8)
        - Wonderful Copenhagen (Box-folder 69/9-10)
    - Hazel Flagg, 1953, Music by Jule Styne, lyrics by Bob Hilliard
      - Miscellaneous music (Box-folder 70/1)
    - Heaven on earth, 1948, Music by Jay Gorney, lyrics by Barry Trivers
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - The apple jack (Box-folder 70/2)
        - A bow in my hair (Box-folder 70/3)
        - Lady police (Box-folder 70/3)
        - Wedding in the park, Laid in: lyric sheets (Box-folder 70/4)
        - You're the first cup of coffee (Box-folder 70/5)
    - The inn people see Mistress of the inn
    - Inside U.S.A., 1948, Music by Arthur Schwartz, lyrics by Howard Dietz
      - Rhode Island is famous for you, Full score-reduced, negative photos (Box-folder 70/6)
    - The king and I, 1951, Music by Richard Rodgers, book and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Script (Box-folder 70/7)
    - Let music ring!, No credits
      - Synopses (Box-folder 70/8)
    - The little prince and the aviator, 1981, Music by John Barry, lyrics by Don Black
      - Full scores
        - The child in the man (Box-folder 120/1)
        - Echo song (Box-folder 120/2)
        - Fanfares (Box-folder 120/3)
        - Fennec exit (Box-folder 120/4)
        - Fennec song (Box-folder 120/5)
        - Fennec's reentrance (Box-folder 120/6)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 120/7)
        - First impressions (Box-folder 120/8)
        - First impressions incidental (Box-folder 120/9)
        - A grain of sand (Box-folder 120/10)
        - I don't regret a thing (Box-folder 120/11)
        - I like my misfortunes to be taken seriously (Box-folder 120/12)
        - I pity the poor poor Parisiennes (Box-folder 120/13)
        - I pity the poor poor Parisiennes, For radio recording (Box-folder 120/14)
        - It was you: (Georges) (Box-folder 120/15)
        - I've got you to thank you for all this (Box-folder 120/16)
        - Little prince (Box-folder 120/17)
        - Little prince finale Act II (Box-folder 120/18)
        - Lotus club (Box-folder 120/19)
        - Making ev'ry minute count (Box-folder 120/20)
        - Orly airport (Box-folder 120/21)
        - Overture (Box-folder 120/22)
        - Par avion (Box-folder 120/23)
        - Par avion reprise (Box-folder 120/24)
        - Par avion underscore (Box-folder 120/25)
        - The planet earth (Box-folder 120/26)
        - Planet finale (Box-folder 120/27)
        - Planet people (Box-folder 120/28)
        - Playground of the planets (Box-folder 120/29)
        - Prelude (Box-folder 120/30)
        - Rich as the bank of France (Box-folder 120/31)
        - Rose ballet (Box-folder 120/32)
        - Rose song (Box-folder 121/1)
        - Rose song reprise (Box-folder 121/2)
        - The rose's good morning (Box-folder 121/3)
        - The snake (Box-folder 121/4)
        - A straw hat and cane song (Box-folder 121/5)
        - Sunet song (Box-folder 121/6)
        - Tea dance (Box-folder 121/7)
        - The volcano song (Box-folder 121/8)
        - The volcano song reprise (Box-folder 121/9)
        - Watch out for the Baobabs (Box-folder 121/10)
        - We couldn't we musn't we won't (Box-folder 121/11)
        - We were made for each other (Box-folder 121/12)
        - Why should I expect a thing (Box-folder 121/13)
        - Wind, sand and stars chorus (Box-folder 121/14)
        - Wind, sand and stars, Includes radio recording version (Box-folder 121/15)
        - The worker's song (Box-folder 121/16)
      - Lead sheets
        - The child in the man (Box-folder 70/9)
        - Echo song (Box-folder 70/10)
        - Fennec song (Box-folder 70/11)
        - A grain of sand (Box-folder 70/12)
        - I don't regret a thing (Box-folder 70/13)
        - I like my misfortunes taken seriously (Box-folder 70/14)
        - I pity the poor poor Parisians (Box-folder 70/15)
        - I've got you to thank for all this (Box-folder 70/16)
        - Par avion (Box-folder 70/17)
        - Par avion reprise (Box-folder 70/18)
        - Playground of the planets (Box-folder 70/19)
        - Rose song (Box-folder 70/20)
        - Rose song reprise (Box-folder 70/21)
        - The snake song (Box-folder 70/22)
        - The stars will be laughing (Box-folder 70/23)
        - A straw hat and cane song (Box-folder 70/24)
        - The volcano song (Box-folder 70/25)
        - Watch out for the Baobabs (Box-folder 70/26)
        - We couldn't we musn't we won't (Box-folder 70/27)
        - Wind, sand and stars (Box-folder 70/28)
        - The worker's song (Box-folder 70/29)
        - Miscellaneous piano scores (Box-folder 70/30)
      - Parts, Incomplete, mostly strings
        - I pity the poor poor Parisiennes (Box-folder 71/1-2)
        - Little prince (Box-folder 71/3)
        - Wind, sand and stars (Box-folder 71/4)
        - Miscellaneous papers (Box-folder 71/5)
    - The loft, circa 1966, Music by Lor Crane, lyrics by Nadine Lewis; Unproduced
      - Lead sheets, Titles include: Artistic bums–opening; Introducing characters; Little town; Artistic bums; Augie’s problem; Sid’s solution to Augie’s problem (Box-folder 71/6)
    - Look Ma, I'm dancin!, 1948, Music and lyrics by Hugh Martin
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Gotta dance (Box-folder 71/7)
        - Horrible, horrible love (Box-folder 71/8)
        - If you'll be mine (Box-folder 71/9)
        - I'm not so bright (Box-folder 71/10)
        - I'm the first girl in the second row in the third scene of the fourth number (Box-folder 71/11)
        - I'm tired of Texas (Box-folder 71/12)
        - Let's do a ballet (Box-folder 71/13)
        - The little boy blues (Box-folder 71/14)
        - Lost in this town (Box-folder 71/15)
        - Lullaby (Box-folder 71/16)
        - Shauny O'Shay (Box-folder 71/17)
        - Tiny room (Box-folder 71/18)
        - The way it might have been (Box-folder 71/19)
        - Orchestration notes (Box-folder 71/20)
    - May wine, 1935, Music by Sigmund Romberg, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, book by Frank Mandel
      - Script (Box-folder 71/21)
    - Memphis bound!, 1945, Music and lyrics by Don Walker, lyrics by Clay Warnick; Based on H.M.S. Pinafore by Gilbert and Sullivan
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Growin' pains (Box-folder 71/22)
        - The Nightingale, the moon and I (Box-folder 71/23)
        - Old love (Box-folder 71/24)
        - Script version I, circa 1943 (Box-folder 71/25)
        - Script version II, circa 1943 (Box-folder 71/26)
    - The mikado, circa 1958, Music by Arthur Sullivan, lyrics by W.S. Gilbert; The following may have been for a planned adaptation titled The cool mikado, circa 1958
      - If your love were mine, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 72/1)
    - Miss Liberty, 1949, Music and lyrics by Irving Berlin
      - Full scores
        - Little fish in a big pond overture, Short score/sketch (Box-folder 72/2)
        - Little fish: Finale Act I (Box-folder 72/2)
        - Overture (Box-folder 72/3)
        - Paris wakes up and smiles, Arranged by Robert Russell Bennett (Box-folder 72/4)
        - What do I have to do to get my picture in the paper? (Box-folder 72/5)
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Falling out of love can be fun (Box-folder 72/6)
        - I love you (Box-folder 72/7)
        - Me an' my bundle (Box-folder 72/8)
    - Mistress of the inn, circa 1957-1961, Alternate title: Sweet mistress; Revised title: The inn people, 1972; Music by Don Walker, lyrics by Ira Wallach
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Act II-scene I (incidental) (Box-folder 72/9)
        - Act II-scene 3 opening (Box-folder 72/10)
        - Ah, tender pain of love (Box-folder 72/11)
        - Alone in a world of men (Box-folder 72/12)
        - Bread and wine and love (Box-folder 72/13)
        - Cavalier's waltz (Box-folder 72/14)
        - A certain something (Box-folder 72/15)
        - Chapter XI (Box-folder 72/16)
        - Chapter XII (Box-folder 72/17)
        - Chapter thirteen (Box-folder 72/18)
        - The count and the marquis (Box-folder 72/19)
        - The curtain's down (Box-folder 72/20)
        - The curtain's up (Box-folder 73/1)
        - Damn all women! (Box-folder 73/2)
        - Divisible by two (Box-folder 73/3)
        - Eve (Box-folder 73/4)
        - Farewell, dear world (Box-folder 73/5)
        - Finale Act II (Box-folder 73/6)
        - Finale-here and now (Box-folder 73/7)
        - Finaletto, Act I (Box-folder 73/8)
        - Flower song (Box-folder 73/9)
        - For womankind, for Italy, for me (Box-folder 73/10)
        - God and the people (Box-folder 73/11)
        - Good-day (Box-folder 73/12)
        - Guiseppe (Box-folder 73/13)
        - Here and now (Box-folder 73/14)
        - Here's to the revolution (Box-folder 73/15)
        - How long can I go on? (Box-folder 73/16)
        - I am who I am (Box-folder 73/17)
        - I'm all right!/I feel well! (Box-folder 73/18)
        - I'm all right! reprise/I feel well! reprise (Box-folder 73/19)
        - In love with a lovely life (Box-folder 74/1)
        - A little gift (Box-folder 74/2)
        - Look for a woman (Box-folder 74/3)
        - Mad! (Box-folder 74/4)
        - Man in a square (Box-folder 74/5)
        - A masculine man (Box-folder 74/6)
        - Mirandolina (Box-folder 74/7)
        - A moderate man (Box-folder 74/8)
        - The monkey in my mind (Box-folder 74/9)
        - My lovely lady (Box-folder 74/10)
        - Nervous (Box-folder 74/11)
        - Never before (Box-folder 74/12)
        - Never let your dander down (Box-folder 75/1)
        - Never let your dander down encore (Box-folder 75/2)
        - Never let your dander down reprise (Box-folder 75/3)
        - O, shed not blood (Box-folder 75/4)
        - Open house, open heart (Box-folder 75/5)
        - Overture (Box-folder 75/6)
        - Passing fancy (Box-folder 75/7)
        - The presence of a violin (Box-folder 75/8)
        - Prison song (Box-folder 75/9)
        - Reminder (Box-folder 75/10)
        - Restless rover (Box-folder 75/11)
        - Revenge! (Box-folder 75/12)
        - Simpatico (Box-folder 75/13)
        - Singing in the street (Miranolina's soliloquy) (Box-folder 75/14)
        - Small but grand (Box-folder 75/15)
        - Something indescribable (Box-folder 76/1)
        - Something indescribable tag (Box-folder 76/2)
        - A stone in my shoe (Box-folder 76/3)
        - Sweet mistress of my heart (Box-folder 76/4)
        - Tan-tivy (Box-folder 76/5)
        - Tension (Box-folder 76/6)
        - The touch (Box-folder 76/7)
        - What can a woman give a man? (Box-folder 76/8)
        - Yes or no/Let it happen now (Box-folder 76/9)
        - Miscellaneous music (Box-folder 76/10)
        - Miscellaneous parts (Box-folder 76/11)
        - Musical and audition routines (Box-folder 76/12)
        - Lyric sheets (Box-folder 76/13)
      - Script material
        - La locandiera
          - Script by Helen Lohmann, translated and adapted by Carlo Goldini, 1927 (Box-folder 76/14)
        - Ah, sweet mistress
          - Script by Don Walker and Ira Wallach, 1957 (Box-folder 76/15)
        - Sweet mistress
          - Script by Don Walker and Ira Wallach, 1958 (Box-folder 77/1)
          - Script by Ira Wallach, 1961 June 20 (Box-folder 77/2)
          - Script by Ira Wallach, 1961 Oct. 15 (Box-folder 77/3)
          - Script by Ira Wallach, 1961 Dec. 6 (Box-folder 77/4)
          - Scripts by Don Walker and Ira Wallach, undated (Box-folder 77/5-78/5)
      - The inn people
        - Script Ira Wallach, Bertram Basford, Arnold Goland, undated (Box-folder 79/1-3)
        - Untitled scripts, fragments, rewrites (Box-folder 79/4)
        - Miscellaneous lead sheets, Titles include: Act I scene II; Fun and games a.k.a. Children’s games; Give me your hand; Inn people; Miranda trio; Nick’s audience address (Box-folder 79/5)
        - Lyric worksheets and superceded lyrics (Box-folder 79/6)
        - Synopses (Box-folder 79/7)
        - Scripts (Box-folder 79/8-9)
        - Script-corrected copy (Box-folder 79/10)
        - Script, 1972 July (Box-folder 80/1)
        - Audition script, 1972 July 8 (Box-folder 80/2)
        - Audition script, 1972 July 18 (Box-folder 80/3)
        - Modern script #3 (Box-folder 80/4)
        - Scripts (Box-folder 80/5-12)
    - The most happy fella, 1956, Music and lyrics by Frank Loesser
      - Eyes like a stranger, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 81/1)
      - Nobody's ever gonna love you like I love you, Piano-conductor score, piano-vocal score (Box-folder 81/2)
    - Music, maestro!, By Don Walker
      - First working synopsis (Box-folder 81/3)
      - Working synopsis, first revision (Box-folder 81/4)
    - Night must fall, 1936, Play by Emlyn Williams with incidental music, composer unknown; There is no indication of what production this might be for
      - Scores for piano, organ and timpani (Box-folder 81/5)
      - Piano/organ parts (Box-folder 81/6)
      - Timpani parts (Box-folder 81/5)
    - Of thee I sing, 1952 revival, Music by George Gershwin, lyrics by Ira Gershwin
      - Full scores
        - Entr'acte (Box-folder 121/17)
        - Exit Atlantic City scene (Box-folder 121/18)
        - Exit march (Box-folder 121/19)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 121/20)
        - Finale Act I tag (Box-folder 121/21)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 121/22)
        - Finale ultimo coda (Box-folder 121/23)
        - Finaletto-scene IV-Act I (Box-folder 121/24)
        - The illegitimate daughter (Box-folder 121/25)
        - Lafayette (Box-folder 121/26)
        - Love is sweeping the country (Box-folder 121/27)
        - Love is sweeping the country intro (Box-folder 121/28)
        - Love is sweeping the country section II (Box-folder 121/29)
        - Love is sweeping the country vocal tag (Box-folder 122/1)
        - Mine (Box-folder 122/2)
        - Mine reprise (Box-folder 122/3)
        - Moving picture scene (Box-folder 122/4)
        - Of thee I sing, Two versions (Box-folder 122/5)
        - Of thee I sing intro (Box-folder 122/6)
        - Opening scene III, Act II (Box-folder 122/7)
        - The president is going to be a daddy! (Box-folder 122/8)
        - Radio opening (Box-folder 122/9)
        - The senate (Box-folder 122/10)
        - Trumpeter blow your garden horn (Box-folder 122/11)
        - Who cares? (Box-folder 122/12)
      - Piano-vocal scores
        - Exit Atlantic City scene (Box-folder 81/8)
        - Finale Act I (Box-folder 81/9)
        - Finale ultimo (Box-folder 81/10)
        - Finaletto scene IV, Act I (Box-folder 81/11)
        - The illegitimate daughter (Box-folder 81/12)
        - Love is sweeping the country (Box-folder 81/13)
        - Love is sweeping the country sect. 2 (Box-folder 81/14)
        - Mine reprise (Box-folder 81/15)
        - Of thee I sing (Box-folder 82/1)
        - Opening Act II (Box-folder 82/2)
        - Opening scene III, Act II (Box-folder 82/3)
        - Overture (Box-folder 82/4)
        - Radio opening (Box-folder 82/5)
        - The senate (Box-folder 82/6)
        - Trumpeter blow your golden horn (Box-folder 82/7)
        - Who cares? (Box-folder 82/8)
        - Who is the lucky girl to be? (Box-folder 82/9)
        - Wintergreen for president (Box-folder 82/10)
        - Miscellaneous music (Box-folder 82/11)
        - Lyric sheets (Box-folder 82/12)
        - Piano-vocal score, Heavily annotated (Box-folder 82/1)
    - On your toes, 1954 revival, Music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Lorenz Hart